Here you would have that and looks like
in a small fishing village in Columbia.
That's the switch. Definitely not a GFI
by the sink. This is decomposing.
Um, there's no top on the toilet. This
is full of paper.
The sink is just
a little bit out of plumb. Um,
there's no soap here.
Here's the light fixture.
This is the mirror.
But wait till you see how the people
react to this.
Yeah.
This is the vibe. Ha!
Everybody's happy. Nobody gives a
about that. They're by the beach and
they're having fun. This is a fantastic
vibe with the [music] best, cheapest,
freshest seafood you'll ever eat. And
nobody gives a about the building
code failures in there. This is how life
should be lived. More fun, less